So now we are going to see how we can find vulnerabilities in mifare classic cards and how to check
the security of our classic cards.
Right.
So the tool we are going to use is known as Prox three.
This is the tool which is used for penetration testing, cloning and simulating RFID tags.
So its price range is around 35 to $190.
Basically, it depends on the device.
So I'm using this is the Chinese version, which is I'm using it's around 35 to $40, but you can also
purchase it from Amazon.
It might cost you around 100 or more, so you have to look for it.
So Mark three used for multiple types of RFID tags and for multiple types of RFID frequencies.
But we are going to use Mark three for Mifare classic cards and see how we can find vulnerabilities
in classic card and and see if we can clone these cards and see other vulnerabilities in classic cards,
Right?
So we will first start by setting up prox mark three.
Then we will also update the firmware of Prox mark three.
Then we will see how to crack card with the manufacturer keys or default keys.
Then we will see how to crack card using single manufacturer key.
After that, we are also going to see how to clone these RFID cards.
Right.
So let's just get started on it.